Edmund B. Chaffee Papers
Edmund B. Chaffee Papers
- Correspondence
  - 1929
    - Fett, Clair B. (Box 19)
    - Fie - Fir (Box 19)
    - Fla - Flo (Box 19)
    - Fos - Fow (Box 19)
    - Fred - Fren (Box 19)
    - Friends Neighborhood Guild (Box 19)
    - Friends Seminary (Box 19)
    - Gai - Gat (Box 19)
    - Gel - Geo (Box 19)
    - George School (Box 19)
    - Gib - Gil (Box 19)
    - Goldman, Leo (Box 19)
    - Gordon, Dugald (Box 19)
    - Gota - Goth (Box 19)
    - Greater New York Federation of Churches, 3 folders (Box 19)
    - Greater New York Taxpayers Association (Box 19)
    - Gro - Gu (Box 19)
    - Hai - Hal (Box 19)
    - Harb - Harr (Box 19)
    - Hartford Seminary Foundation (Box 19)
    - Hars - Has (Box 19)
    - Hea - Hes (Box 19)
    - Hillman, Alexander (Box 19)
    - Hold - Holm (Box 19)
    - Holmes, John Haynes, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Holmes, Richard S. (Box 19)
    - Holt, Henry and Company (Box 19)
    - Hopkins, J. A. H. (Box 19)
    - Hum - Huy (Box 19)
    - Inn - Inq (Box 19)
    - Intef - Intern (Box 19)
    - Italian Chamber of Labor (Box 19)
    - Jac - Jap (Box 19)
    - Jelliffe, W. R. (Box 19)
    - Joi - Jos (Box 19)
    - Kahon, Henry Q., Assemblyman, State of New York (Box 19)
    - Kanagawaken-Kyosaikai (Association for Social Work) (Box 19)
    - Kee - Kes (Box 19)
    - Kimball, Emily (Box 19)
    - Klinger, Charles (Box 19)
    - Knight, Walter D. (Box 19)
    - Knop - Knot (Box 19)
    - Kre - Kri (Box 19)
    - L. T. Building Corporation (Box 19)
    - Labor Temple
      - Affirmations, Notices of Church Services and Responses, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Annual Reports, Statements, Audits (Box 19)
      - Budget, Allocation of Funds, Finances, 3 folders (Box 19)
      - Committee Meetings, Notices and Responses, Arrangements for, 3 folders (Box 19)
      - Contributions to, Appeals and Responses, Thank You Notes, 6 folders (Box 19)
      - Employment Inquiries and Recommendations, 3 folders (Box 19)
      - Employment Inquiries and Recommendations January-May, 3 folders (Box 20)
      - Employment Inquiries and Recommendations June-December, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Maintenance and Repairs, Supplies and Equipment, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Programs and Activities, 9 folders (Box 20)
      - Solicitations for Temple Business (Box 20)
      - Work Schedules and Instructions to Personnel, 4 folders (Box 20)
    - Labor Temple, East 84th Street (Box 20)
    - Lak - Lay (Box 20)
    - Lea - Lee (Box 20)
    - Leiper, H. S. (Box 20)
    - Lewis, J. (Box 20)
    - Lib - Lit (Box 20)
    - Llano - Lloyd (Box 20)
    - Lor - Low (Box 20)
    - Mac - Mag (Box 20)
    - Mai - Man (Box 20)
    - Mar - Mat (Box 20)
    - McAlpin, Charles W. (Box 20)
    - McAf - McAl (Box 20)
    - McC - McM (Box 20)
    - Med - Mer (Box 20)
    - Methodist Episcopal Church (Box 20)
    - Meyers Invention (Box 20)
    - Mie - Mil (Box 20)
    - Mod - Mur (Box 20)
    - Muste, A. J. (Box 20)
    - Nag - National C (Box 20)
    - National F - W (Box 20)
    - Nea - Nel (Box 20)
    - New York A - B (Box 20)
    - New York, City of (Box 20)
    - New York E - Sc (Box 20)
    - New York Sk - State C. (Box 20)
    - New York State Department of Labor (Box 20)
    - New York T - U (Box 20)
    - Newa - Newt (Box 20)
    - Niebuhr, Reinhold (Box 20)
    - Noble, Charles - H. W. (Box 20)
    - Nolting, Edward L. (Box 20)
    - North - Northfield (Box 20)
    - Nye, Gerald P., Senator (Box 20)
    - O'Brien, Dave (Box 20)
    - Ohori, Reverend E. A. (Box 20)
    - Open Forum Speakers' Bureau (Box 20)
    - Open Road, The (Box 20)
    - Outlook Company, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Page, Kirby (Box 21)
    - Par - Pas (Box 21)
    - Pat - Pax (Box 21)
    - Pea - Peo (Box 21)
    - Perkins, Margaret - R. O. (Box 21)
    - Pioneer Youth of America (Box 21)
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America (Box 21)
    - Presbyterian Church in the United States of America
      - Board of Christian Education (Box 21)
      - Board of Foreign Missions (Box 21)
      - Board of National Missions (Box 21)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 21)
    - Presbyterian Union of New York City (Box 21)
    - Presbytery of Cincinnati, Board of National Missions and Church Extensions (Box 21)
    - Presbytery of New York
      - Church Extension Committee
        - Savage, T. F., Secretary, 3 folders (Box 21)
        - Merle-Smith, Treasurer (Box 21)
      - Committee on Program and Field Activities (Box 21)
      - Department of Christian Education (Box 21)
      - Mendenhall, H. G., Stated Clerk, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 21)
    - Ralston, Mrs. E. S. (Box 21)
    - Randolph, A. Philip (Box 21)
    - Reade, Mrs. Cordelia (Box 21)
    - Reconciliation Trips (Box 21)
    - Reese, Charles (Box 21)
    - Richards, Edward C. M. January, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Richards, George H. (Box 21)
    - Righter, Miss (Box 21)
    - Robb - Rock (Box 21)
    - Rogers, Florence - Noah (Box 21)
    - Rom - Roy (Box 21)
    - Rul - Rus (Box 21)
    - San - Sar (Box 21)
    - Sawyer, Roland D., Congressman, Massachusetts (Box 21)
    - Sayre Family (Box 21)
    - Sche - Schl (Box 21)
    - Schmalhausen, Samuel D., 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Sco - Scr (Box 21)
    - Sea - Sen (Box 21)
    - Sha - She (Box 21)
    - Sil - Sin (Box 21)
    - Smith, L. R. - Tucker (Box 21)
    - Soc - Sol (Box 21)
    - Spa - Speed (Box 21)
    - Speers, Thomas Guthrie (Box 21)
    - Spinnato, Joseph P. (Box 21)
    - Stel - Stev (Box 21)
    - Stewart, George (Box 21)
    - Stone, Hannah M. (Box 21)
    - Strac - Straff (Box 21)
    - Straton, John Roach (Box 21)
    - Strong, Sydney (Box 21)
    - Str - Stu (Box 21)
    - Sulzberger, Mrs. Cyrus L. (Box 21)
    - Talmage, Mr. David H. (Box 21)
    - Tea - Tel (Box 21)
    - Theta (Box 21)
    - Thomas, Norman (Box 21)
    - Thorne, Reverend Frederick R. (Box 21)
    - Tinker, Mr. W. H. (Box 21)
    - Trimble, Mrs. William S. (Box 21)
    - Tucker, Mrs. William Ellsworth (Box 21)
    - Twitchell, Mr. and Mrs. Hanford M. (Box 21)
    - Tynes, Wendell (Box 21)
    - Unif - Union S (Box 21)
    - Union Theological Seminary, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, 3 folders (Box 21)
    - Universal - University (Box 21)
    - Valentines Day Committee (Box 21)
    - Venus, Mr. A. (Box 21)
    - Villelli, Mr. Joseph A. (Box 21)
    - Vollenweider, Mr. John A. (Box 21)
    - W E V D (Box 22)
    - Wagner, Robert, Senator (Box 22)
    - Waid, D. Everett (Box 22)
    - Wal - Wat (Box 22)
    - Wef - Wei (Box 22)
    - Wel - Wes (Box 22)
    - White - Whito (Box 22)
    - Wille - Willi (Box 22)
    - Woj - Wom (Box 22)
    - Woo - Wor (Box 22)
    - Y.M.C.A., 3 folders (Box 22)
    - Y.W.C.A. (Box 22)
    - Unidentified (Box 22)
  - 1930
    - Action Membership Corporation (Box 22)
    - A.I.C.P. (Box 22)
    - Alb - All (Box 22)
    - American A - C (Box 22)
    - American E - U (Box 22)
    - Apel, Marie (Box 22)
    - Artist's Council (Box 22)
    - Association of Advertising Men (Box 22)
    - Atlantic Monthly, The (Box 22)
    - Bai - Ban (Box 22)
    - Barb - Barr (Box 22)
    - Beattie, Reverend Lee W. (Box 22)
    - Beck, G. F. (Box 22)
    - Becke - Ber (Box 22)
    - Birm - Birt (Box 22)
    - Blake, Harry (Box 22)
    - Blanchard, Mrs. W. O. (Box 22)
    - Blanshard, Paul (Box 22)
    - Bog - Bor (Box 22)
    - Bow - Boy (Box 22)
    - Bro - Bru (Box 22)
    - Buc - Bur (Box 22)
    - Butt - Butz (Box 22)
    - Car - Caw (Box 22)
    - Chaffee, Family of, 4 folders (Box 22)
    - Char - Chi (Box 22)
    - Christian Century, The (Box 22)
    - Christian Union Quarterly, The (Box 22)
    - Church - Churchman (Box 22)
    - Citi - City (Box 22)
    - Cia - Cle (Box 22)
    - Cli - Clu (Box 22)
    - Coe, William W. (Box 22)
    - Coffin, Henry Sloan (Box 22)
    - Cog - Col (Box 22)
    - Committee - Community (Box 22)
    - Con - Cope (Box 22)
    - Copeland, Royal S., Senator (Box 22)
    - Cou - Cox (Box 22)
    - Cra - Cro (Box 22)
    - Cum - Cur (Box 22)
    - Davis, Jerome (Box 22)
    - De Nanny, Francis G. (Box 22)
    - Discussion Guild (Box 22)
    - Dodd - Dodds (Box 22)
    - DuB - Dunn (Box 22)
    - Durant, Will (Box 22)
    - Eby, Louise (Box 22)
    - Edd - Edu (Box 22)
    - Ell - Elm (Box 22)
    - Elmore, Carl (Box 22)
    - Ennist, Robert G. (Box 22)
    - Equitist, The (Box 22)
    - Evans, Reverend A. H. (Box 22)
    - Farb - Farr (Box 22)
    - Federal Council of Churches (Box 22)
    - Fellowship of Faiths (Box 22)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Fenner Brockway Dinner Committee (Box 23)
    - Fie - Fit (Box 23)
    - Flanagan, Sue (Box 23)
    - Floral Hill High School (Box 23)
    - Forbes and Company, H. C. (Box 23)
    - Fosdick, Harry Emerson (Box 23)
    - Fou - Fox (Box 23)
    - French, Fred-Lawrence (Box 23)
    - Friends of the Soviet Union (Box 23)
    - Friends Seminary (Box 23)
    - Frisbee, Frances Young Peoples’ Society (Box 23)
    - Ful - Fur (Box 23)
    - Gai - Gar (Box 23)
    - Gei - Ger (Box 23)
    - Gilb - Gill (Box 23)
    - Golden Rule Foundation (Box 23)
    - Gordon, Dugald (Box 23)
    - Gordon, Mary (Box 23)
    - Goss, Isaac (Box 23)
    - Graham, Stella F. (Box 23)
    - Greater New York Federation of Churches (Box 23)
    - Greenwich House - Greenwich House Workshops (Box 23)
    - Hai - Han (Box 23)
    - Harbison, William (Box 23)
    - Harkness, Edward S. (Box 23)
    - Harp - Harr (Box 23)
    - Hartford Seminary (Box 23)
    - Hartl - Haz (Box 23)
    - Hea - Hey (Box 23)
    - Hoa - Hoe (Box 23)
    - Hofstader, Samuel H., New York State Senator (Box 23)
    - Holmes, John Haynes (Box 23)
    - Hol - How (Box 23)
    - Hum - Hut (Box 23)
    - Imes, William Lloyd (Box 23)
    - Inq - Ins (Box 23)
    - International Ladies' - Unemployed (Box 23)
    - Isaacs, Martin (Box 23)
    - Italian Settlement, The (Box 23)
    - Jac - Jam (Box 23)
    - Jennings, Pauline (Box 23)
    - Joh - Jon (Box 23)
    - Kahan, Henry O., New York State Assemblyman (Box 23)
    - Kammerer, Rafael (Box 23)
    - Kei - Kej (Box 23)
    - Kips Bay Neighborhood Association (Box 23)
    - Kling, Phina (Box 23)
    - Knic - Knig (Box 23)
    - Koval, Philip (Box 23)
    - L. T. Building Corporation (Box 23)
    - Labor Temple
      - Affirmations, Notices of Church Services, Responses, 2 folders (Box 23)
      - Annual Reports, Statements, Audits Budget, Allocation of Funds, Finances (Box 23)
      - Committee Meetings, Notices and Responses, Arranged for (Box 23)
      - Contributions to, Appeals and Responses, Thank You Notes, 2 folders (Box 23)
      - Employment Inquiries, Recommendations, 2 folders (Box 23)
      - Maintenance and Repairs, Supplies and Equipment, 2 folders (Box 23)
      - Programs and Activities, 6 folders (Box 23)
      - Solicitations for Temple Business (Box 23)
      - Work Schedules and Instructions to Personnel, 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Labour Party, The (Box 23)
    - La Guardia, Fiorello, Congressman (Box 23)
    - L'Am - Law (Box 23)
    - Lea - Lew (Box 23)
    - Listener's Club, The (Box 23)
    - Loo - Low (Box 24)
    - Luccock, Halford S. (Box 24)
    - Lyford, Oliver S. (Box 24)
    - Macc - Man (Box 24)
    - Mar - May (Box 24)
    - McA - McG (Box 24)
    - McGinnies, Joseph A., New York State Assemblyman (Box 24)
    - McGr - Mek (Box 24)
    - Merrill, William P. (Box 24)
    - Methodist - Episcopal Church (Box 24)
    - Mil - Mis (Box 24)
    - Moak Printing Company (Box 24)
    - Moffat, Abbot Low, New York State Assemblyman (Box 24)
    - Mon - Mot (Box 24)
    - Mue - Mul (Box 24)
    - Muste, A. J. (Box 24)
    - Muthu, C. (Box 24)
    - Nation - National U. (Box 24)
    - Nea - New M. (Box 24)
    - New York A - M (Box 24)
    - New York, City of (Municipal Government Listings) (Box 24)
    - New York City S - New York L. (Box 24)
    - New York, State of (Government Listings) (Box 24)
    - New York T - U (Box 24)
    - Newell, Reverend Frederick (Fritz) (Box 24)
    - Nieubuhr, Lydia G. (Box 24)
    - Noble, Charles C. (Box 24)
    - Nolting, Edward L. (Box 24)
    - Nye, Gerald P., Senator (Box 24)
    - O'Brien - Rex, Daniel (Box 24)
    - Orphal, Reverend Alfred John (Box 24)
    - Oul - Out (Box 24)
    - Pad - Pap (Box 24)
    - Par - Pay (Box 24)
    - Pfeiffer, Timothy Newell (Box 24)
    - Pel - Per (Box 24)
    - Pic - Pitt (Box 24)
    - Pon - Pop (Box 24)
    - Powys, John Cowper (Box 24)
    - Presbyterian Church in the United States of America
      - Board of National Missions (Box 24)
      - Board of Pensions (Box 24)
      - Synod of New York (Box 24)
    - Presbyterian Union of New York City (Box 24)
    - Presbytery of Baltimore (Box 24)
    - Presbytery of Chicago (Box 24)
    - Presbytery of Milwaukee (Box 24)
    - Presbytery of New York
      - Church Extension Committee
        - Merle-Smith, Treasurer (Box 24)
        - Savage, Theodore F., Secretary, 2 folders (Box 24)
        - Mendenhall, Stated Clerk (Box 24)
        - Social Service Committee (Box 24)
    - Prine - Print (Box 24)
    - Psychological Corporation, The (Box 24)
    - Quill Club, The (Box 24)
    - Ramb - Rams (Box 24)
    - Reade, Cordelia (Box 24)
    - Reconciliation Trips (Box 24)
    - Red - Rev (Box 24)
    - Richard, R. - Riv. (Box 24)
    - Richards, Edward C. M. (Box 24)
    - Richards, George H., 3 folders (Box 24)
    - Roe - Ros (Box 24)
    - Rutgers Presbyterian Church, David Russell, Minister (Box 24)
    - Rybicki, Edward C. (Box 24)
    - Saint John - Sayre (Box 24)
    - Sch - Sco (Box 24)
    - Searles, W. G. (Box 24)
    - Sha - Sho (Box 24)
    - Sie - Sin (Box 24)
    - Sma - Smy (Box 24)
    - Soc - Sol (Box 24)
    - Speers, Thomas Guthrie (Box 24)
    - Spinnato, Joseph (Box 24)
    - Spoerie, Raymond L. (Box 24)
    - Sta - Ste (Box 24)
    - Sti - Stoc (Box 24)
    - Stone, Drs. Abraham and Hannah (Box 24)
    - Strong, Sydney (Box 24)
    - Survey Graphic and Survey Midmonthly (Box 24)
    - Talbott, George H. (Box 24)
    - Teachers' Union, The (Box 24)
    - Theta (Box 25)
    - Thilin, Georges (Box 25)
    - Thomas, Norman (Box 25)
    - Thomp - Thu (Box 25)
    - Tippy, Worth M. (Box 25)
    - Unif - Union S. (Box 25)
    - Union Theological Seminary, 3 folders (Box 25)
    - United Hospital Fund (Box 25)
    - United Neighborhood Houses (Box 25)
    - United States Daily, The (Box 25)
    - United States Department of Labor (Box 25)
    - United States, Government of, Hoover, Herbert - President (Box 25)
    - Universal - University (Box 25)
    - Van D - Vang (Box 25)
    - Veach, Robert Wells (Box 25)
    - Villard, Oswald Garrison (Box 25)
    - Vondermuhll, Mrs. Kate (Box 25)
    - Wagner, Robert, Senator (Box 25)
    - Wai - Wan (Box 25)
    - War Registers' League (Box 25)
    - Wate - Watt (Box 25)
    - Wef - Wev (Box 25)
    - Wheeler, Burton K., Senator (Box 25)
    - White, F - R (Box 25)
    - White, Walter, N.A.A.C.P., Acting Secretary (Box 25)
    - Whittaker, George (Box 25)
    - Wic - Wis (Box 25)
    - Women's Peace Union (Box 25)
    - Woolton, Barbara (Box 25)
    - Workers' Education Bureau of America, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - World C - World (Box 25)
    - Wronker, Louis J., Alderman, New York City (Box 25)
    - Wylie, Dwight (Box 25)
    - Yergin, Reverend Howard V. (Box 25)
    - Young, Reverend Bradford (Box 25)
    - Y.M.C.A., 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Y.W.C.A. (Box 25)
    - Unidentified (Box 25)
    - To and From Others (Box 25)
  - 1931
    - Abingdon Press, The (Box 25)
    - Adult Education Association, The (Box 25)
    - Affiliated Summer Schools for Women Workers in Industry (Box 25)
    - Ainslie, Peter (Box 25)
    - Ali - All (Box 25)
    - American A - W (Box 25)
    - Anti-Saloon League of New York (Box 25)
    - Aohenz, Mildred P. (Box 25)
    - Apel - Apeli (Box 25)
    - Arb - Arn (Box 25)
    - Association for Jewish Colonization in the Soviet Union, Incorporated (Box 25)
    - Austin Advertising Agency (Box 25)
    - Ball - Barn (Box 25)
    - Barr - Bau (Box 25)
    - Beacon Press, The (Box 25)
    - Beck, G. F. (Box 25)
    - Becker - Benedict (Box 25)
    - Bennett, John C. (Box 25)
    - Bennett, Vincent - Ber (Box 25)
    - Berman, Max (Box 25)
    - Bin - Bir (Box 25)
    - Blac - Bland (Box 25)
    - Blanshard, Paul, City Affairs Committee of New York (Box 25)
    - Blod - Bloo (Box 25)
    - Bnais Israel Old Age Home (Box 25)
    - Bor - Bow (Box 25)
    - Bre - Brons (Box 25)
    - Bronx - Broo (Box 25)
    - Brot - Brown, C. S., Jr. (Box 25)
    - Brown, H. - Bru (Box 25)
    - Buc - But (Box 25)
    - Cald - Carm (Box 25)
    - Carnegie C. - Cav (Box 25)
    - Carnegie, Mrs. Andrew (Box 25)
    - Central E. - T. (Box 25)
    - Chaffee, Family of January-November, 4 folders (Box 25)
    - Chaffee, Family of December (Box 26)
    - Chap - Chas (Box 26)
    - Che - Chi (Box 26)
    - Christian Century, The, 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Christian H - Chu (Box 26)
    - Citi - City (Box 26)
    - Cla - Cli (Box 26)
    - Coe - Coffe (Box 26)
    - Coffin, Henry Sloan (Box 26)
    - Col - Commi (Box 26)
    - Commu - Conf (Box 26)
    - Cong - Coo (Box 26)
    - Copeland, Royal S., Senator (Box 26)
    - Correlated Graphic Arts (Box 26)
    - Cors - Cou (Box 26)
    - Cra - Cro (Box 26)
    - Curr - Cust (Box 26)
    - Dar - David (Box 26)
    - Davis, Jerome (Box 26)
    - Daw - Day (Box 26)
    - Dec - Dew (Box 26)
    - Dixon, Mrs. Joseph West (Box 26)
    - Dodge, Astrid M. (Box 26)
    - Drysdale, Euphemia (Box 26)
    - Dub - Dun (Box 26)
    - Ear - Eat (Box 26)
    - Eddy, Sherwood (Box 26)
    - Edg - Edi (Box 26)
    - Einstein World Peace Fund (Box 26)
    - Elli - Ely (Box 26)
    - Ema - Emergency U. (Box 26)
    - Emergency Work Bureau (Box 26)
    - Ennis, John (Box 26)
    - Equitist, The (Box 26)
    - Erie Chapel Institute, The (Box 26)
    - Essex County Council of Religious Education (Box 26)
    - Evans, Jessie (Box 26)
    - Executive Service - Executives & Foremans (Box 26)
    - Farb - Farr (Box 26)
    - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America, 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Federat - Fei (Box 26)
    - Fellowship of Faiths (Box 26)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation (Box 26)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation, International (Box 26)
    - Ferris, Mrs. Joseph W. (Box 26)
    - Fie - Fin (Box 26)
    - Flanagan, Sue (Box 26)
    - Flood, Arthur F. (Box 26)
    - Foreign Affairs Forum (Box 26)
    - Fre - Friends O. (Box 26)
    - Friends Seminary (Box 26)
    - Gala - Gall (Box 26)
    - German Consulate General (Box 26)
    - Gillmore, Maria (Box 26)
    - Gol - Goo (Box 26)
    - Gordon, Dugald (Box 26)
    - Graham, Stella S. (Box 26)
    - Greater New York Federation of Churches (Box 26)
    - Greater Protestant Social Service (Box 26)
    - Greater New York Interfaith Committee (Box 26)
    - Gundlach, Laura (Box 26)
    - Hab - Hai (Box 26)
    - Hall, Cameron (Box 26)
    - Hall, W. - Hard (Box 26)
    - Harkness, Edward S. (Box 26)
    - Harr - Hay (Box 26)
    - Hea - Hes (Box 26)
    - Hill - Hillm (Box 26)
    - Hodson, John Edward (Box 26)
    - Holmes, John Haynes, 3 folders (Box 26)
    - Holmes, Richard S. (Box 26)
    - Hoh - How (Box 27)
    - Hue - Hunter, J. (Box 27)
    - Hunter, S. - Hut (Box 27)
    - Imes, W. L. (Box 27)
    - Imr - Inn (Box 27)
    - Ins - Io (Box 27)
    - Jac - Jan (Box 27)
    - Jaquith, Harold C. (Box 27)
    - Jenk - Jenne (Box 27)
    - Jennings, Pauline - Ruth (Box 27)
    - Joh - Joi (Box 27)
    - Jones, Philip C. (Box 27)
    - Jump, Herbert A. (Box 27)
    - Kaufman, Abraham (Box 27)
    - Kel - Ken (Box 27)
    - Kim - Kir (Box 27)
    - Kjellstrom, Erik (Box 27)
    - Klo - Klu (Box 27)
    - Kni - Kno (Box 27)
    - Kre - Kro (Box 27)
    - L. T. Building Corporation, 2 folders (Box 27)
    - Labor Temple
      - Affirmations, Notices of Church Services, Responses (Box 27)
      - Budget, Allocation of Funds, Finances, 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Committee Meetings, Notices and Responses, Arrangements for (Box 27)
      - Contributions to, Appeals and Responses, Thank You Notes (Box 27)
      - Employment Inquiries and Recommendations, 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Maintenance and Repairs, Supplies and Equipment, 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Programs and Activities, 8 folders (Box 27)
      - Solicitations for Temple Business (Box 27)
      - Work Schedules and Instructions to Personnel, 3 folders (Box 27)
    - Lac - Lat (Box 27)
    - Leag - Leav (Box 27)
    - Led - Lei (Box 27)
    - Lie - Lit (Box 27)
    - Ler - Low (Box 27)
    - Lyf - Lyo (Box 27)
    - MacC - Mas (Box 27)
    - McAlpin, Charles (Box 27)
    - McConnell, Francis J., Bishop, Methodist Episcopal Church (Box 27)
    - McCr - McD (Box 27)
    - Med - Mez (Box 27)
    - Mic - Miller, K. D. (Box 27)
    - Miller, M. - Mit (Box 28)
    - Moa - Mou (Box 28)
    - Mullins, Mrs. W. H. (Box 28)
    - Muste, A. J. (Box 28)
    - Myers, Dr. Thomas (Box 28)
    - Nas - National Conference (Box 28)
    - National Cou - National U (Box 28)
    - Nea - New Wo (Box 28)
    - New York A - B (Box 28)
    - New York City
      - City of (Box 28)
      - Mission Society, Jelliffe, W. R., Executive Vice-President (Box 28)
    - New York Committee of One Thousand (Box 28)
    - New York Con - L (Box 28)
    - New York, State Department of Social Welfare (Box 28)
    - New York T - U (Box 28)
    - Newman, Samuel (Box 28)
    - Nic - Nis (Box 28)
    - Nol - Noy (Box 28)
    - Nuovo Mundo, Il (Box 28)
    - O’B - Op (Box 28)
    - Outlook, The (Box 28)
    - Pag - Pax (Box 28)
    - Pea - Penno (Box 28)
    - Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of (Box 28)
    - Peo - Pet (Box 28)
    - Pioneer Youth of America (Box 28)
    - Platt, Joseph E. (Box 28)
    - Poo - Pos (Box 28)
    - Presbyterian Church in the United States of America
      - Board of Christian Education (Box 28)
      - Board of National Missions, 3 folders (Box 28)
      - Board of Pensions Hubbard Press (Box 28)
      - Office of Moderator (Box 28)
    - Presbyterian Ministers Fund (Box 28)
    - Presbyterian Union of New York City (Box 28)
    - Presbytery of Cincinnati, Ohio (Box 28)
    - Presbytery of New York
      - Church Extension Committee
        - Savage, Theodore F. Secretary, 2 folders (Box 28)
        - Merle-Smith Treasurer (Box 28)
      - Committee on Evangelism (Box 28)
      - Department of Christian Education (Box 28)
      - Social Service Committee, Jelliffe, W. R., Chairman, 3 folders (Box 28)
      - Mendenhall, R.G., Stated Clerk (Box 28)
      - Youth of New York (Box 28)
    - Presbytery’s Committee of the Board of Pensions (Box 28)
    - Pride of Judea Orphan’s Home (Box 28)
    - Protestant Charities Commission (Box 28)
    - Protestant S. - Prov. (Box 28)
    - Pyle, Stephen L. (Box 28)
    - Que - Qui (Box 28)
    - Ram - Ran (Box 28)
    - Reconciliation trips, 4 folders (Box 28)
    - Ree - Rey (Box 28)
    - Rice - Richards, A. (Box 28)
    - Richards, Edward C. M. (Box 28)
    - Richards, George H. January-April, 4 folders (Box 28)
    - Richards, George H. May-December, 5 folders (Box 29)
    - Ril - Riv (Box 29)
    - Rog - Rom (Box 29)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., New York State Governor (Box 29)
    - Rose - Ross (Box 29)
    - Russell, Ga - Ge (Box 29)
    - Russell, Reverend William K. (Box 29)
    - Ryd - Ryl (Box 29)
    - Sal - Sau (Box 29)
    - Sav - Say (Box 29)
    - Scha - Schm (Box 29)
    - Searle, Robert W. (Box 29)
    - Schorr, Jack (Box 29)
    - Sill - Six (Box 29)
    - Smith, Frank - Fred (Box 29)
    - Soc - Sou (Box 29)
    - Spe - Spi (Box 29)
    - Ste - Sto (Box 29)
    - Str - Stu (Box 29)
    - Suf - Sur (Box 29)
    - Tag - Tay (Box 29)
    - Tel - Ter (Box 29)
    - Theta (Box 29)
    - Thomas, Norman (Box 29)
    - Thomas, W. L. – W. T. (Box 29)
    - Tillinghast, R. C. (Box 29)
    - Tolman, Wilmer C. (Box 29)
    - Tra - Tru (Box 29)
    - Tumia, Emanuel (Box 29)